hikarabita kotoba wo tsunai de
connecting old words that have been used up
soredemo bokura shinpuru na omoi wo tsutaetai dake na no
I just want to convey my simple thoughts
fukinukeru kusunda ano hi no kaze wa
that day's faint wind blows away
kinou no haikyo ni uchi sutete
at the castle ruins of yesterday
kimi to warau ima wo ikiru no da
I'll laugh with you and live for the moment
soredemo ano dekigoto ga kimi wo kurushimeru daro
still that incident will continue to trouble you, right?
dakarakoso sayonara nanda
that's why it must be good-bye
konomama nanimo nokorazu ni anata to wakachiau dake
leaving nothing behind, let us share what is left
yagate bokura wa sore ga subetee dato kigatsuite
in time, we'll realize that it was everything
kanashimi wa hoo wo tsutatte namida no kawa ni naru dake
and sadness will touch our cheeks, creating a river of tears
yureru omoi wa tsuyoi uzu ni natte tokeau no yo
Trembling thoughts swept into a vortex and melting away
I'll let you out of here.
And I'll grant you one wish too.
You don't have to worry.
Your strong will is going to remain
as Residual Aura inside me.
It's not like you'll lose everything.
Now then your flesh is mine.
With this, Orochimaru-sama's body
has once again
become unable to reanimate
for several years.
However, there's a next time...
I-Indeed. My body no longer has value
as a vessel for Reanimation Jutsu.
It will now be difficult for me
who has lost everything...
to find my own calling.
I've finally understood that.
Even if it's not me...
I'll bring in the new "vessel"
even if it costs me my life.
That's my repayment to
Orochimaru-sama.
That's the only redemption for me...
who was worthless.
Mistake!
A New Enemy
They're fast.
Akamaru.
Come quick after you've set the bombs!
Oh no!
— All right.
— Great.
Akamaru, well done.
Messing with me.
Akamaru.
Don't you "arf" me, you mutt!
I'll waste you.
Hold on.
You!
Kiba! Akamaru!
Damn it.
What's happening?
You punks!
Where are Kiba and Akamaru?!
Another one's come.
We have no choice.
I'll take care of this so you take
the coffin and go on ahead.
Shikamaru...
Get going already.
Wh-Why are you...?
I'm sorry, Naruto.
It's my miscalculation.
Kimimaro.
You were taking too long, Tayuya.
And what happened to
the other three?
Being none other than those
of the former "Sound Ninja Five."
Why are you...?
Your body... Your body's no longer...
I'm not moving with the flesh anymore.
It's mental power.
Man, you cheater of death...
I understand a little now
that feeling...
of being information that has escaped
from the prison of the flesh.
The feeling of experiencing
a taste of Orochimaru-sama's dream.
Orochimaru...!
This vessel... is an important vessel
for the dream...
The flesh that Orochimaru-sama
truly desires.
But you guys were a bit too late.
Some dangerous guy
has appeared again.
That air about him is
nothing ordinary.
Anyway, we need
to sort out the situation.
If we were to carelessly
plunge in...
You jerk.
What're you babbling nonsense?
Naruto!
Give back Sasuke!
Hey wait!
Tayuya.
The reason why I won't kill you now
is because you have a mission
you have to complete.
And my mission is to deliver
that to Orochimaru-sama.
Isn't it too late now?
Humph. I told you.
That's the body that Orochimaru-sama
truly desires.
The next vessel, huh?
That's right...
And this is the only thing that
I can do at present.
I leave those two pieces
of garbage to you.
Sasuke...
That punk!
Calm down, Naruto.
How can I calm down?
At this rate,
Sasuke will get far away again.
Naruto's right.
This is a mission to bring Sasuke back
to the Leaf Village.
We must choose what would be
the most rational means
to execute the mission.
Damned punks.
I'll finish this in a flash.
Naruto, listen up.
Please move according to the plan
that I'm going to tell you.
He's a classic close-range
combat-type fool
with Shadow Clone Jutsu
as his only saving grace.
And he's a middle-range
combat type
who binds his enemies with
a Jutsu using shadows...
and a sharp squad leader, huh?
Got it?
Yeah.
Come on already you punks.
It's two versus one.
We've got the upper hand.
It's an opponent we can beat
if we team up.
Let's go, Naruto.
All right.
With garbage like you jerks,
it doesn't matter how many
of you are there.
Don't underestimate our teamwork.
Let's go!
Bring it.
Now... Naruto.
I'll blow you away.
Gotcha. The strategy is a success.
Farewell.
Damn.
You tricked me.
Teamwork, my ass. You little punks...
Damn.
You wouldn't fall for the same trick
over and over, huh..?
Small fry... You've got nerve.
Well, I guess I'll settle for just
having been able to let him get away.
Remember this.
It's not just Jutsu that are weapons.
I'm counting on you, Shikamaru.
Hang in there, Sasuke.
But that kid,
how wonderful it is that
he can move with that body, eh?
Kabuto, I don't know what kind
of order you gave him,
but it's a bit harsh.
Not at all.
It wasn't an order.
I don't like to force things.
He acted on his own.
For you whom he reveres.
Kabuto... You've really got
a hateful personality, don't you?
Orochimaru-sama.
To you,
Kimimaro was a perfect existence...
His thoughts were steeped in darkness
in the same way as yours.
And he sanctified you.
And he fanatically admired
and revered you.
Moreover, he was of the Shinobi clan
with the strongest and perfect bodies
being the legitimate bloodline
of their Kekkai Genkai...
until a short time ago.
Yes...
When I think about having lost him
I still get a chill down my spine.
I think about it even now...
The man I truly wished for...
The body I wanted the most... Kimimaro.
And if only he hadn't been stricken
with disease
the assassination of the Hokage
would've gone smoother.
Seal!
My arms...
Now... you can no longer use
either of your arms...
And since you can't use your arms
you can't weave Sign...
You no longer possess Ninjutsu!
Your ambition of crushing
the Hidden Leaf... dies right here!
Orochimaru, you fool...
It's unfortunate that we can't leave
together but my disciple...
Let's meet in the other world
one day...
Sasuke...
Sasuke-kun's not here yet?
We wouldn't have needed to go
through such an experience.
In the world very often things don't go
as we want them to.
It's only a matter of time,
Orochimaru-sama.
When Tayuya... comes back
I'll kill her.
Hold it.
Hey...!
Now then, how shall I defeat you?
You...
Those eyes...
It seems he possesses
a peculiar Chakra.
What does Orochimaru want to do...?
Why's he after Sasuke?
Orochimaru-sama has already
obtained Immortality Jutsu...
A long time is necessary to get every Jutsu
and obtain everything in the world.
What does that have to do
with Sasuke?!
"Immortal" doesn't mean that
the flesh is being maintained as is...
Before his body decays
a strong and new flesh will be made
into a vessel for his soul.
That's...
Are you saying that's Sasuke?!
Yes... That's right.
I won't let such a thing happen!
Idiot... What will come of sending
one shrimp punk in pursuit?
And looking at things
in terms of time
up until now you probably sacrificed
one member each time
in order for the group
to move forward.
Is that guy called Sasuke
that important?
How many of your men do you intend
to sacrifice for the sake of just one person?
You incompetent punk.
Heh... Indeed...
For me this is my first mission
as a platoon leader.
It's very disquieting having
comrades gradually whittled down
and I didn't know if my own judgments
were correct or not.
As a squad leader with
the lives of the party in my hands...
respecting the lives in
the four-member party
rather than the life of one person
taken by the enemy...
and deciding to abort a mission
that's too dangerous would be by the book.
Then why didn't you do that?
The world doesn't go
by the book very often...
Since not one person in my squad
would do something like
abandon a captured comrade and give up
fighting for the sake of their own safety.
Me included.
Being the cloud-loving loafer myself,
I am not cut out to be a squad leader
who gives orders to comrades.
The only thing I can do for them...
is to have faith in them.
Listen. I'm not thinking anything
like they were sacrifices.
I'm not thinking anything
like they've died.
Don't mock my comrades.
I got you.
Summoning Jutsu!
This doesn't... look so good.
I'll play a melody of death for you.
Don't you mock us,
you damned punk.
I won't let you take Sasuke
no matter what.
Interesting.
hajimete kimi to shabetta
for the first time I spoke to you
kimi wa waratte kureta
and you smiled
hajimete kimi to shabereta
for the first time I was able to speak
boku no kono kotoba de
in my own words
boku nanka ga shaberi kaketara meiwaku ni omou ka na
would you think it was a bother if I approached you?
sonna fuan o kakaete yuuki o dashite mita yo
despite my doubts I worked up my courage
umaku shaberenai boku no fukiyou na hanashi
my clumsy attempts with words
kimi wa mimi o sorasazu ni chanto kiite kureta yo
you listened without turning away
sore dake de boku wa ukarete shimau no sa
no wonder I get carried away by you
dakedo kimi wa boku nante nantomo omottenai yo ne
but you don't feel anything for me do you?
setsunai yo
I feel so sad
dakedo
but...
hajimete kimi to shabetta
for the first time I spoke to you
kimi wa waratte kureta
and you smiled
hajimete kimi to shabereta
for the first time I was able to speak
boku no kono kotoba de
in my own words
hajimete kimi to shabetta
for the first time I spoke to you
kimi wa waratte kureta
and you smiled
hajimete kimi to shabereta
for the first time I was able to speak
boku no kono kotoba de
In my own words
hajimete kimi to shabetta
for the first time I spoke to you
Damn it! What'll I do?!
He's trouble enough yet
his Chakra has increased
several ten-fold!
It's no good. I can't use it here yet.
But if I stay like this we'll...
I get it, Akamaru.
It's like you said.
I have no choice but to use it!
Next time:
"Roar! Howl! The Ultimate Tag."